LOUISE EASTERBROOK

61+481353826

Web Developer

☐ louise.easterbrook@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am Macquarie University Web and Mobile App Development student that has just completed my degree in November this year. I have three years' experience working with web development tools and I am very eager to exercise and expand my current skill set within a working role.

EDUCATION

Macquarie University - Bachelor of Information Technology March 2019 - November 2021

- Majoring in Web and Mobile App Development
- Distinction Average
- Identified as a top performing student in second and third year app development units

SKILLS

- Portfolio Link: https://louiseeasterbrook.netlify.app/
- Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Java, Python
- Frameworks/Libraries: React.js, Node.js, Express, jQuery
- Databases: MongoDBVersion Control: Git/GitHub

WORK HISTORY

- Team Member: Cherrybrook Primary OOSH Care July 2019 current
 - o Responsible for managing a group of children
 - o Completing Paperwork for each child
 - o Planning weekly activities
- Team Member: Skypeak Adventures

April 2017 - September 2019

- o Responding to any customer needs
- o Responsible for harnessing and inducting customers into the course
- o Responsible for opening and closing and all included procedures
- Team Member: Peak Pursuits

April 2017 - February 2018

- o Responsible for introducing customers to the centre
- o Responsible for harnessing and inducting customers into the course